<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Briefly Remembered</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2025</copyright>
    <managingEditor>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com (Optimus Prime)</managingEditor>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Optimus Prime</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Optimus Prime</itunes:author>
    <description><![CDATA["Briefly Remembered: 3 Minute Obituaries" is a poignant and concise podcast series that pays tribute to the lives of remarkable individuals who have left an indelible mark on the world. Each episode, lasting just three minutes, captures the essence of a person's journey, highlighting their achievements, challenges, and lasting legacy. 

This series offers a unique blend of past legends and contemporary icons. From Hollywood mavericks and sports legends to musical prodigies and cultural icons, each episode provides a snapshot of a life well-lived. Whether it's the fearless final act of Val Kilmer, the eternal glory of Gary Carter, or the transformative impact of Irv Gotti, "Briefly Remembered" ensures that the memories of these incredible individuals are preserved and celebrated.

In addition to honoring past legends, the podcast also features brand new episodes every time someone famous passes away, ensuring that the series remains timely and relevant. Perfect for a quick listen during a commute, a break, or anytime you need a moment of reflection, "Briefly Remembered" offers a concise yet profound way to remember and celebrate the lives of those who have shaped our world.]]></description>
    <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Three minute podcast episodes celebrate notable lives through concise tributes and timely remembrances of famous figures.]]></itunes:summary>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    <image>
      <url>https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png</url>
      <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
      <title>Briefly Remembered</title>
    </image>
    <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture &gt; History, News &gt; Obituaries, Arts &gt; Biography"/>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
    <item>
      <title>Edgar Lungu: From Military Lawyer to President: Breaking Barriers in Zambian Leadership (1956-2025)</title>
      <itunes:title>Edgar Lungu: From Military Lawyer to President: Breaking Barriers in Zambian Leadership (1956-2025)</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[Step into the compelling journey of Edgar Lungu, Zambia's sixth president whose recent passing marks the end of a remarkable chapter in African leadership. From his humble beginnings as a military lawyer to becoming the nation's head of state, Lungu's story embodies the transformative power of perseverance and public service. This episode delves into his unprecedented rise to presidency following Michael Sata's death in 2015, his groundbreaking appointment of Inonge Wina as Zambia's first female Vice President, and his ambitious infrastructure development initiatives that reshaped the nation's landscape. We explore the complexities of his leadership, from successful resolution of mining sector challenges that preserved thousands of jobs to the economic challenges that marked his final years in office. His presidency, concluding with the democratic transition to Hakainde Hichilema in 2021, left an indelible mark on Zambian politics. Through intimate accounts and historical analysis, we examine how Lungu's legacy, cut short by his passing in June 2025, reflects both the achievements and challenges of modern African leadership, offering valuable insights into the evolving nature of democracy in sub-Saharan Africa.

Further Reading:
• 'Against All Odds: Zambia's President Edgar Chagwa Lungu's Rough Journey to State House' - Book
• 'What are President Edgar Lungu's achievements?' (https://www.lusakatimes.com/2015/08/25/what-are-president-edgar-lungus-achievements/)
• 'Zambia: A Deep Dive into Edgar Lungu Divisive Legacy' (https://www.whoownsafrica.com/magazine/zambia-a-deep-dive-into-edgar-lungu-divisive-legacy/)
• 'Former Zambian President Edgar Lungu Dies at Age 68' (https://www.bbrief.co.za/2025/06/06/edgar-lungu/)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Delve into the legacy of Edgar Lungu, Zambia's sixth president who made history by appointing the nation's first female vice president during his transformative 2015-2021 tenure.]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Step into the compelling journey of Edgar Lungu, Zambia's sixth president whose recent passing marks the end of a remarkable chapter in African leadership. From his humble beginnings as a military lawyer to becoming the nation's head of state, Lungu's story embodies the transformative power of perseverance and public service. This episode delves into his unprecedented rise to presidency following Michael Sata's death in 2015, his groundbreaking appointment of Inonge Wina as Zambia's first female Vice President, and his ambitious infrastructure development initiatives that reshaped the nation's landscape. We explore the complexities of his leadership, from successful resolution of mining sector challenges that preserved thousands of jobs to the economic challenges that marked his final years in office. His presidency, concluding with the democratic transition to Hakainde Hichilema in 2021, left an indelible mark on Zambian politics. Through intimate accounts and historical analysis, we examine how Lungu's legacy, cut short by his passing in June 2025, reflects both the achievements and challenges of modern African leadership, offering valuable insights into the evolving nature of democracy in sub-Saharan Africa.

Further Reading:
• 'Against All Odds: Zambia's President Edgar Chagwa Lungu's Rough Journey to State House' - Book
• 'What are President Edgar Lungu's achievements?' (https://www.lusakatimes.com/2015/08/25/what-are-president-edgar-lungus-achievements/)
• 'Zambia: A Deep Dive into Edgar Lungu Divisive Legacy' (https://www.whoownsafrica.com/magazine/zambia-a-deep-dive-into-edgar-lungu-divisive-legacy/)
• 'Former Zambian President Edgar Lungu Dies at Age 68' (https://www.bbrief.co.za/2025/06/06/edgar-lungu/)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="http://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749255962/airtable_audio/wndloqpmldy1udhfmtix.mp3" 
                 length="1351385" 
                 type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recwDFmTLIOr3ngdl</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2 min 49 sec</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Barnett: From &quot;Fall Back Baby&quot; Jump Shot to Doctor&apos;s Degree: The Knicks Legend Who Conquered Court and Classroom (1936-2025)</title>
      <itunes:title>Dick Barnett: From &quot;Fall Back Baby&quot; Jump Shot to Doctor&apos;s Degree: The Knicks Legend Who Conquered Court and Classroom (1936-2025)</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[Explore the extraordinary journey of Dick Barnett, whose legendary "Fall Back Baby" jump shot and relentless pursuit of excellence transcended the basketball court. From his humble beginnings in Gary, Indiana, to becoming a pivotal figure in the New York Knicks' golden era, Barnett's story embodies the perfect fusion of athletic prowess and academic achievement. This episode delves into his remarkable career at Tennessee A&I State, where he led his team to three consecutive NAIA championships, before ascending to NBA stardom with the Knicks, contributing to their historic championship victories in 1970 and 1973. Beyond his athletic achievements, we explore Barnett's groundbreaking transition from hardwood hero to academic scholar, earning his doctorate and championing education. His legacy, immortalized by his retired #12 jersey and 2024 Basketball Hall of Fame induction, serves as a testament to his dual impact as both a basketball pioneer and educational advocate. Through archival footage and personal accounts, we examine how Barnett's determination to excel both on and off the court has inspired generations and redefined the possibilities for professional athletes pursuing academic excellence.

Further Reading:
• 'The Dream Whisperer' - Documentary Film
• 'HBCU Legend: Dick Barnett's Basketball Journey' (https://www.nba.com/news/qa-dick-barnett-hbcus-nba-playing-days)
• 'Breaking Barriers: The Dick Barnett Story' (https://news.fordham.edu/fordham-magazine/catching-up-with-new-york-knicks-legend-dick-barnett/)
• 'From Court to Classroom: Dr. Barnett's Legacy' (https://eshemagazine.com/2021/05/dr-dick-barnett-talks-about-legendary-basketball-career-and-the-dr-richard-barnett-foundation/)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Explore the legacy of Dick Barnett, the New York Knicks legend who won two NBA championships, earned his doctorate, and inspired generations both on and off the court.]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the extraordinary journey of Dick Barnett, whose legendary "Fall Back Baby" jump shot and relentless pursuit of excellence transcended the basketball court. From his humble beginnings in Gary, Indiana, to becoming a pivotal figure in the New York Knicks' golden era, Barnett's story embodies the perfect fusion of athletic prowess and academic achievement. This episode delves into his remarkable career at Tennessee A&I State, where he led his team to three consecutive NAIA championships, before ascending to NBA stardom with the Knicks, contributing to their historic championship victories in 1970 and 1973. Beyond his athletic achievements, we explore Barnett's groundbreaking transition from hardwood hero to academic scholar, earning his doctorate and championing education. His legacy, immortalized by his retired #12 jersey and 2024 Basketball Hall of Fame induction, serves as a testament to his dual impact as both a basketball pioneer and educational advocate. Through archival footage and personal accounts, we examine how Barnett's determination to excel both on and off the court has inspired generations and redefined the possibilities for professional athletes pursuing academic excellence.

Further Reading:
• 'The Dream Whisperer' - Documentary Film
• 'HBCU Legend: Dick Barnett's Basketball Journey' (https://www.nba.com/news/qa-dick-barnett-hbcus-nba-playing-days)
• 'Breaking Barriers: The Dick Barnett Story' (https://news.fordham.edu/fordham-magazine/catching-up-with-new-york-knicks-legend-dick-barnett/)
• 'From Court to Classroom: Dr. Barnett's Legacy' (https://eshemagazine.com/2021/05/dr-dick-barnett-talks-about-legendary-basketball-career-and-the-dr-richard-barnett-foundation/)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="http://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749327076/airtable_audio/ynl26l9lqfdpu8jkql0e.mp3" 
                 length="1369231" 
                 type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recfgMalKVTcvvgmm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2 min 51 sec</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein: From Elite Finance to Federal Scandal: A Financier&apos;s Notorious Fall (1953-2019)</title>
      <itunes:title>Jeffrey Epstein: From Elite Finance to Federal Scandal: A Financier&apos;s Notorious Fall (1953-2019)</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[Delve into the complex and controversial story of Jeffrey Epstein, a former financier whose rise to wealth and subsequent downfall shocked the world. This episode examines Epstein's trajectory from his humble beginnings in Brooklyn to his ascent in Wall Street's elite circles, and ultimately, his dramatic fall from grace. We explore how he transformed from a mathematics teacher at Manhattan's prestigious Dalton School into a powerful financial figure, cultivating connections with prominent individuals across business, politics, and entertainment. The narrative takes a dark turn as we investigate the serious criminal allegations that led to his 2008 conviction in Florida and his final arrest in 2019 on federal sex trafficking charges. The episode concludes with a detailed examination of the circumstances surrounding his death in custody at the Metropolitan Correctional Center and the subsequent investigations that revealed systematic failures within the federal prison system. Recent developments, including the Department of Justice's ongoing release of declassified files, continue to shed new light on this complex case that has implications reaching the highest levels of society.

Further Reading:
• 'Filthy Rich: Jeffrey Epstein' - Documentary Series
• 'Perversion of Justice: The Jeffrey Epstein Story' - Book
• 'DOJ Releases First Phase of Declassified Epstein Files' (https://abcnews.go.com/US/doj-releases-phase-epstein-files-including-evidence-list/story?id=119274954)
• 'The Epstein Investigation: Complete Coverage' (https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/press-release/file/1180481/dl)
• 'Understanding the Epstein Case Timeline' (https://abcnews.go.com/alerts/jeffreyepstein)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Examining the controversial life of Jeffrey Epstein, from his rise as a prominent financier to his downfall amid federal sex trafficking charges and death in custody.]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Delve into the complex and controversial story of Jeffrey Epstein, a former financier whose rise to wealth and subsequent downfall shocked the world. This episode examines Epstein's trajectory from his humble beginnings in Brooklyn to his ascent in Wall Street's elite circles, and ultimately, his dramatic fall from grace. We explore how he transformed from a mathematics teacher at Manhattan's prestigious Dalton School into a powerful financial figure, cultivating connections with prominent individuals across business, politics, and entertainment. The narrative takes a dark turn as we investigate the serious criminal allegations that led to his 2008 conviction in Florida and his final arrest in 2019 on federal sex trafficking charges. The episode concludes with a detailed examination of the circumstances surrounding his death in custody at the Metropolitan Correctional Center and the subsequent investigations that revealed systematic failures within the federal prison system. Recent developments, including the Department of Justice's ongoing release of declassified files, continue to shed new light on this complex case that has implications reaching the highest levels of society.

Further Reading:
• 'Filthy Rich: Jeffrey Epstein' - Documentary Series
• 'Perversion of Justice: The Jeffrey Epstein Story' - Book
• 'DOJ Releases First Phase of Declassified Epstein Files' (https://abcnews.go.com/US/doj-releases-phase-epstein-files-including-evidence-list/story?id=119274954)
• 'The Epstein Investigation: Complete Coverage' (https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/press-release/file/1180481/dl)
• 'Understanding the Epstein Case Timeline' (https://abcnews.go.com/alerts/jeffreyepstein)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="http://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749326121/airtable_audio/d0d2bwrfzhu8v7ni0ftz.mp3" 
                 length="1060308" 
                 type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">reclAfeVGZvjxmR83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2 min 13 sec</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gary Carter: Baseball&apos;s Eternal &quot;Kid&quot; Who Caught Glory Behind the Plate (1954-2012)</title>
      <itunes:title>Gary Carter: Baseball&apos;s Eternal &quot;Kid&quot; Who Caught Glory Behind the Plate (1954-2012)</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[Step behind the mask with baseball's most charismatic catcher as we explore the extraordinary legacy of Gary Carter, whose infectious smile and boundless enthusiasm earned him the endearing nickname "The Kid." From his humble beginnings in Culver City, California, to his pinnacle moment in the 1986 World Series with the New York Mets, Carter revolutionized the catching position with unprecedented defensive excellence and remarkable offensive prowess. His stellar 19-year career showcased both technical mastery – leading National League catchers in putouts eight times and setting a record with just one passed ball in 1978 – and offensive firepower, accumulating 2,092 hits and earning 11 All-Star selections. As the first Hall of Famer enshrined wearing a Montreal Expos cap, Carter's impact transcended team loyalties, earning him three Gold Gloves and establishing him among the top ten catchers in baseball history. Beyond the statistics, Carter's lasting legacy lies in his transformative leadership, demonstrated most notably during the Mets' historic 1986 championship run, and his unwavering positive spirit that continued to inspire even through his courageous battle with brain cancer until his passing in 2012. His story embodies the perfect blend of athletic excellence and personal character that defines baseball's greatest heroes.

Further Reading:
• 'Still a Kid at Heart: My Life in Baseball and Beyond' - Book
• 'The Gamer' - Book
• 'Above All Else, Gary Carter Played Hard' (https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2011/05/31/above-all-else-gary-carter-played-hard/)
• 'The Magical Years of "The Kid"' (http://1970sbaseball.mlblogs.com/2015/02/16/the-magical-years-of-the-kid-gary-carter/)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Explore the legacy of Gary "Kid" Carter, the Hall of Fame catcher who led the Mets to World Series glory and became the first Montreal Expo enshrined in Cooperstown.]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Step behind the mask with baseball's most charismatic catcher as we explore the extraordinary legacy of Gary Carter, whose infectious smile and boundless enthusiasm earned him the endearing nickname "The Kid." From his humble beginnings in Culver City, California, to his pinnacle moment in the 1986 World Series with the New York Mets, Carter revolutionized the catching position with unprecedented defensive excellence and remarkable offensive prowess. His stellar 19-year career showcased both technical mastery – leading National League catchers in putouts eight times and setting a record with just one passed ball in 1978 – and offensive firepower, accumulating 2,092 hits and earning 11 All-Star selections. As the first Hall of Famer enshrined wearing a Montreal Expos cap, Carter's impact transcended team loyalties, earning him three Gold Gloves and establishing him among the top ten catchers in baseball history. Beyond the statistics, Carter's lasting legacy lies in his transformative leadership, demonstrated most notably during the Mets' historic 1986 championship run, and his unwavering positive spirit that continued to inspire even through his courageous battle with brain cancer until his passing in 2012. His story embodies the perfect blend of athletic excellence and personal character that defines baseball's greatest heroes.

Further Reading:
• 'Still a Kid at Heart: My Life in Baseball and Beyond' - Book
• 'The Gamer' - Book
• 'Above All Else, Gary Carter Played Hard' (https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2011/05/31/above-all-else-gary-carter-played-hard/)
• 'The Magical Years of "The Kid"' (http://1970sbaseball.mlblogs.com/2015/02/16/the-magical-years-of-the-kid-gary-carter/)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="http://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749242270/airtable_audio/yiiglvhkqwfon8kkclcu.mp3" 
                 length="1254769" 
                 type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rec0yzyxss1wbuU01</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2 min 37 sec</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter S. Thompson: The Gonzo Revolutionary Who Made Journalism Wild (1937-2005)</title>
      <itunes:title>Hunter S. Thompson: The Gonzo Revolutionary Who Made Journalism Wild (1937-2005)</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[Step into the wild world of Hunter S. Thompson, the revolutionary journalist who transformed American media with his audacious "Gonzo" style of storytelling. From his Kentucky roots to his final days in Colorado, this episode delves into the life of a literary maverick who dared to blur the lines between observer and participant. We explore how Thompson's military experience as a sports editor sparked his journalistic journey, leading to his groundbreaking immersion with the Hell's Angels and the creation of his masterpiece "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas." His unique approach to journalism, where the writer becomes an active character in the story, shattered traditional reporting conventions and birthed a new genre that continues to influence modern media. Through his fearless pursuit of truth and his raw, unfiltered narrative style, Thompson captured the essence of American counterculture during some of the nation's most turbulent decades. Despite personal struggles in his later years, including various health complications, he remained prolific until his death in 2005, contributing regular columns to ESPN.com that showcased his enduring wit and insight. Thompson's legacy extends far beyond his tragic end, living on through generations of writers who embrace his bold, subjective approach to storytelling and his unwavering commitment to exposing the raw truth of American life.

Further Reading:
• 'Gonzo: The Life of Hunter S. Thompson' - Book
• 'Buy the Ticket, Take the Ride: Hunter S. Thompson on Film' - Documentary
• 'The Kentucky Derby Is Decadent and Depraved' (https://sensitiveskinmagazine.com/the-kentucky-derby-is-decadent-and-depraved-hunter-s-thompson/)
• 'Fear, Loathing and the Birth of Gonzo' (https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/fear-loathing-and-the-birth-of-gonzo-72030/)
• 'The Art of Journalism: Writing and Reporting' (https://www.theatlantic.com/entertainment/archive/2012/07/hunter-s-thompsons-advice-for-aspiring-writers/259472/)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Delve into the legacy of Hunter S. Thompson, the audacious creator of Gonzo journalism who revolutionized literary reporting through his immersive, counterculture masterpieces.]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Step into the wild world of Hunter S. Thompson, the revolutionary journalist who transformed American media with his audacious "Gonzo" style of storytelling. From his Kentucky roots to his final days in Colorado, this episode delves into the life of a literary maverick who dared to blur the lines between observer and participant. We explore how Thompson's military experience as a sports editor sparked his journalistic journey, leading to his groundbreaking immersion with the Hell's Angels and the creation of his masterpiece "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas." His unique approach to journalism, where the writer becomes an active character in the story, shattered traditional reporting conventions and birthed a new genre that continues to influence modern media. Through his fearless pursuit of truth and his raw, unfiltered narrative style, Thompson captured the essence of American counterculture during some of the nation's most turbulent decades. Despite personal struggles in his later years, including various health complications, he remained prolific until his death in 2005, contributing regular columns to ESPN.com that showcased his enduring wit and insight. Thompson's legacy extends far beyond his tragic end, living on through generations of writers who embrace his bold, subjective approach to storytelling and his unwavering commitment to exposing the raw truth of American life.

Further Reading:
• 'Gonzo: The Life of Hunter S. Thompson' - Book
• 'Buy the Ticket, Take the Ride: Hunter S. Thompson on Film' - Documentary
• 'The Kentucky Derby Is Decadent and Depraved' (https://sensitiveskinmagazine.com/the-kentucky-derby-is-decadent-and-depraved-hunter-s-thompson/)
• 'Fear, Loathing and the Birth of Gonzo' (https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/fear-loathing-and-the-birth-of-gonzo-72030/)
• 'The Art of Journalism: Writing and Reporting' (https://www.theatlantic.com/entertainment/archive/2012/07/hunter-s-thompsons-advice-for-aspiring-writers/259472/)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="http://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749236286/airtable_audio/yirfjbkualpdps75vzhz.mp3" 
                 length="1257231" 
                 type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recjlGBYRp21N3ige</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2005 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2 min 37 sec</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>obituaries,history,biography,memorials,briefly remembered</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749248313/uuf16a7bldsc4mecqrm1.png"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>