<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Beneath the Noise</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily podcast blending ancient Stoic wisdom with modern challenges through brief contemplative episodes and philosophical reflections.</itunes:summary>
    <description>In a world of constant noise and reactivity, "Beneath the Noise" offers a daily sanctuary for the thoughtful soul. This unique podcast bridges ancient Stoic wisdom with modern challenges, delivering bite-sized episodes that help listeners find clarity and purpose in their daily lives. Through carefully selected quotes from Marcus Aurelius, Epictetus, Seneca, and other Stoic philosophers, each 3-5 minute episode creates a contemplative space where timeless wisdom meets contemporary reality.

Host-guided reflections connect age-old philosophical principles to current events and cultural moments, revealing the unchanging patterns of human experience. Rather than adding to the chaos of news cycles, the podcast uses these events as mirrors, helping listeners understand how Stoic practices can guide us through fear, uncertainty, and change. Each episode's elegant structure - moving from a powerful quote through mindful silence to practical application - creates a consistent ritual that grounds and centers.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750338769/airtable_audio/reciiOKAtKLOigee5-bbe5d.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Philosophy > Self-Help, Education > Personal Development, Religion & Spirituality > Philosophy" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/beneath-the-noise.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>