<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Briefly Remembered</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Three minute podcast episodes celebrating remarkable lives and legacies through intimate biographical storytelling.</itunes:summary>
    <description>In a world that moves at lightning speed, Briefly Remembered offers a thoughtful pause to honor remarkable lives in just three minutes. Each episode crafts an intimate portrait of individuals who've left an indelible mark on our world, from Hollywood legends and sports icons to cultural pioneers and artistic visionaries. Through carefully curated storytelling, the podcast captures the essence of each person's journey, their triumphs, challenges, and the legacy they've left behind.

This dynamic series combines timeless tributes to past legends with timely episodes commemorating recent losses in our cultural landscape. Whether you're discovering the untold stories of yesterday's icons or reflecting on the passing of contemporary figures, Briefly Remembered delivers concise yet profound narratives that celebrate human achievement and resilience. Perfect for busy listeners seeking meaningful content, these three-minute episodes transform daily moments into opportunities for reflection and inspiration.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by artificial intelligence.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750189997/airtable_audio/recHpAZ1RskwZ5q9c-f375d.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Society & Culture > History, News > Obituaries, Arts > Biography" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/briefly-remembered.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>