<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crazy Guys Podcast</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>High energy hosts explore everyday topics with unbridled enthusiasm and unconventional perspectives for entertaining discussions.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Join the wildest ride in podcasting with Crazy Guys Podcast, where everyday topics transform into extraordinary adventures. Each episode dives deep into life's most intriguing subjects, exploring them through an unfiltered lens of pure, unbridled enthusiasm. From mind-bending discussions to hilarious takes on daily experiences, this show delivers entertainment that breaks all conventional boundaries.

Get ready for an adrenaline-pumping journey as our hosts tackle one crazy topic at a time, bringing their signature high-energy style to conversations that will leave you both enlightened and entertained. Whether you're a thrill-seeker, a curious mind, or someone who just loves to laugh, Crazy Guys Podcast offers an escape from the ordinary into a world where wild times reign supreme.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750739609/airtable_audio/recruWeR84hfoHRTu-94d90.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Comedy, Arts > Comedy, Society & Culture > Comedy" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/crazy-guys-podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>