<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Croissants and Castles</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>American family explores European destinations through relatable US comparisons in bite sized travel guides.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Join the Sargent family as they bridge the cultural gap between American life and European adventures in this intimate travel series. Through carefully crafted comparisons between familiar US locations and iconic European destinations, each episode delivers practical insights and atmospheric observations perfect for summer family travel. From comparing Parisian sunsets to Santa Monica's golden hour, to finding echoes of Georgia's forests in Germany's Black Forest, this series transforms seemingly distant European experiences into accessible, relatable adventures for American families planning their own overseas journeys.

Weaving together historical context, contemporary observations, and practical summer travel tips, each 5-7 minute episode serves as both a practical guide and atmospheric companion. Whether you're actively planning a European vacation or simply dreaming of distant shores, these bite-sized episodes offer a unique perspective on experiencing Europe through an American lens.

Disclaimer: This podcast description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors or inconsistencies with actual travel experiences.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="" />
    <itunes:category text="Travel > Family Travel, Travel > Destinations & Culture, Education > Travel Guides" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/croissants-and-castles.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>