<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cue the Cards</title>
    <link></link>
    <language>en</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>AI powered comedy show delivers short daily monologues blending classic late night humor with modern trends.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Step into a time machine where classic late-night comedy meets cutting-edge AI technology. Cue the Cards delivers daily doses of witty observations and punchy punchlines, channeling the golden age of television monologues for today's podcast generation. Each 3-5 minute episode serves up 8-12 carefully crafted jokes about current events, delivered with the smooth, charismatic charm of a vintage talk show host who somehow knows about TikTok trends and viral tweets.

Unlike traditional comedy podcasts that rely on banter and guest interviews, Cue the Cards strips the format down to its essence: setup, punchline, and that perfectly timed pause that lets the joke land. The AI host brings a uniquely charming perspective to daily headlines, combining the dry wit of Johnny Carson with the processing power of modern machine learning. Whether you're commuting, taking a coffee break, or just need a quick laugh, this innovative series proves that artificial intelligence can master the very human art of comedy.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email></itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="" />
    <itunes:category text="Comedy > Stand-Up, Technology > Podcasting, Arts > Performing Arts" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/cue-the-cards.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>