<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Did You Know THAT?!</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Three minute daily podcast revealing fascinating facts and hidden histories about everyday objects and rituals.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Step into a world of daily discoveries with "Did You Know THAT?!", where the ordinary transforms into the extraordinary in just three minutes. Each episode peels back the layers of everyday life, revealing mind-blowing facts and fascinating histories hiding in plain sight. From the secret lives of common objects to the unexpected origins of daily rituals, this podcast delivers bite-sized bursts of wonder that will transform how you see the world around you.

Join our engaging narrator for a daily dose of "wow" moments that turn mundane observations into extraordinary revelations. Whether uncovering the ancient stories behind your morning routine or exposing the surprising science in your kitchen drawer, each compact episode packs a powerful punch of knowledge that will make you the most interesting person in any conversation.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by artificial intelligence.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749951996/airtable_audio/recenJmvMx4bGucGV-f32e3.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Education > How To, Society & Culture > Documentary, Science > Life Sciences" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/did-you-know-that.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>