<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mets Report</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/apprnmgBvtYIQBQbT/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily podcast delivering comprehensive New York Mets coverage through game analysis insider updates and fan perspectives.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Step into the heart of Queens with Mets Report, your essential daily companion for everything New York Mets. From crucial game recaps to insider analysis, this podcast delivers comprehensive coverage of the orange and blue, synthesizing perspectives from trusted beat writers, social media buzz, and official team communications. Each episode breaks down the latest developments, diving deep into player performances, strategic decisions, and the stories that shape the team's journey.

Whether you're dissecting last night's extra-inning thriller or exploring the implications of the latest roster move, Mets Report combines statistical insight with passionate fandom. Host commentary weaves together multiple sources - from New York Post headlines to Reddit theories, Twitter trends to SNY highlights - creating a complete picture of the Mets' universe that goes beyond basic box scores.

Disclaimer: This podcast is independently produced and is not affiliated with the New York Mets, Major League Baseball, or any of their partners. All statistics and information are gathered from publicly available sources.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>Neel.Ketkar@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750051483/airtable_audio/recpKzLmIHFbQlPqA-760bb.jpg" />
    <itunes:category text="Sports > Baseball, News > Sports News, Sports > Sports Commentary" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/mets-report.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>