<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Dad WLA</title>
    <link></link>
    <language>e</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Millennial dad navigates LA parenthood trading beach life for cultural adventures with his toddler.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Join a millennial father's journey through the eclectic landscape of West Los Angeles parenthood, where stroller-friendly museum visits replace surf sessions and food truck adventures become family traditions. This refreshingly honest series explores the unique challenges and unexpected joys of raising a child in LA's cultural hub, offering a perspective that trades beach life for gallery walks and playground politics.

Each episode immerses listeners in vivid, relatable moments of modern fatherhood, from navigating trendy restaurants with a toddler to discovering family-friendly hidden gems across the city. Through candid storytelling and immersive scenarios, this podcast creates a authentic community for dads who prefer LACMA to lifeguard towers and find their parenting groove in LA's vibrant inland neighborhoods.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email></itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="" />
    <itunes:category text="Parenting > Fatherhood, Arts > Places & Travel, Society & Culture > Relationships" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/new-dad-wla.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>