<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>podc</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily five minute horoscope podcast blending astrological guidance with modern culture for Aries listeners.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Welcome to "Aries: Your Daily Horoscope," where cosmic wisdom meets contemporary culture in a fresh, dynamic way. Each day, this bite-sized astrological guide connects planetary movements with current events, viral moments, and cultural phenomena, delivering personalized insights for the bold and ambitious Aries spirit. In just 5-7 minutes, you'll receive a celestial snapshot that's both spiritually grounded and culturally relevant, helping you navigate your day with cosmic confidence.

From breaking news to trending memes, each episode weaves together astrological wisdom with the pulse of modern life. Starting with a powerful cold open that sets the day's emotional tone, followed by precise planetary insights and sign-specific guidance, the show culminates in a memorable "Mood Spell" - a daily mantra that distills cosmic wisdom into one shareable moment.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750316067/airtable_audio/recJFmq4V2Z8Nd4VZ-1077c.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Religion & Spirituality > Spirituality, Arts > Personal Journals, Comedy > Comedy Interviews" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/podc.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>