<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Scandal</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/apprnmgBvtYIQBQbT/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily podcast exploring historical scandals and controversies with modern relevance through expert storytelling and analysis.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Step into the shadowy world of scandal, corruption, and controversy with The Daily Scandal, a riveting podcast that uncovers a new tale of deception, power, and human fallibility every single day. Each meticulously researched episode transports listeners through time to witness history's most compelling scandals, from political conspiracies and corporate frauds to entertainment industry upheavals and societal controversies that changed the course of history.

With a journalist's precision and a storyteller's flair, The Daily Scandal delivers concise yet comprehensive narratives that fit perfectly into your daily routine. Each episode connects these historical misdeeds to contemporary issues, demonstrating how the echoes of past scandals continue to resonate in our modern world. Through dramatic cold opens, expert storytelling, and thoughtful analysis, the podcast reveals not just what happened, but why it matters today.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="" />
    <itunes:category text="News > True Crime, History > Modern, Society & Culture > Documentaries" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/the-daily-scandal.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>