<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Curious Cases of Vera and Nina</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/apprnmgBvtYIQBQbT/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>Optimus Prime</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Two sister sleuths solve neighborhood mysteries with their pets in Santa Monica's Sunset Park.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Join the delightful adventures of Vera and Nina, two young sister sleuths who turn their charming Sunset Park neighborhood in Santa Monica into a playground of mystery and discovery. Twelve-year-old Vera and her nine-year-old sister Nina, accompanied by their loyal beagle Bean and the theatrical squirrel Herman, tackle the most peculiar puzzles their community has to offer.

From schoolyard conundrums to park predicaments and neighborhood enigmas, each episode follows this endearing team as they piece together unusual clues and uncover the secrets that make their little corner of the world so special. With a perfect blend of local charm, heartwarming moments, and unexpected twists, these young detectives prove that even the smallest mysteries can lead to the biggest adventures.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Optimus Prime</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>neel.ketkar@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750009187/airtable_audio/recRYs7dkDyg2IHeU-2db27.jpg" />
    <itunes:category text="Kids & Family > Stories for Kids, Arts > Podcasts, Comedy > Comedy Fiction" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/the-curious-cases-of-vera-and-nina.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>