<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>The 3-Minute Handyman</title>
    <link></link>
    <language>e</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily three minute episodes teach practical DIY home repairs with expert guidance and tool recommendations.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Get ready to become your home's hero with The 3-Minute Handyman, your daily dose of quick, practical DIY solutions. Each weekday, dive into laser-focused episodes that tackle one specific household challenge, from squeaky doors to dripping faucets. With clear instructions, expert tool recommendations, and real-world sound effects, you'll master home maintenance skills in the time it takes to brew your morning coffee.

Whether you're a DIY novice or a weekend warrior, this podcast delivers actionable advice without the fluff. Each episode follows a crisp, consistent format: a clear introduction, detailed instructions, relevant safety tips, and specific tool recommendations. Themed weeks focusing on plumbing, doors and windows, and other common areas help you build your expertise systematically. With episodes released Monday through Friday, you'll quickly develop the confidence to tackle household repairs like a pro.

Disclaimer: This description is experimental and was generated by AI. It may contain factual errors.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email></itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="" />
    <itunes:category text="Home & Garden > Home Repair, Education > How To, Arts > Design & Crafts" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/the-3-minute-handyman.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>