<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>TLDR</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <managingEditor>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com (Optimus Prime)</managingEditor>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/tldr" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Optimus Prime</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Optimus Prime</itunes:author>
    <description><![CDATA[Your morning coffee isn't complete without your daily tech fix. TLDR delivers the biggest tech stories in exactly 3 minutes - because who has time for those 2000-word think pieces? From Silicon Valley shake-ups to the latest AI chaos, crypto drama to startup scandals, we break down what actually matters in the tech world.

Every weekday, TLDR: Tech Lowdown, Daily Rundown serves up the perfect mix of need-to-know news and "wait, what?!" moments that'll make you sound like the smartest person in your Slack channels. No jargon, no fluff, no long-winded explanations - just clear, quick, and occasionally quirky updates on the tech stories everyone will be talking about.

Whether you're a crypto believer, startup hustler, or just someone who wants to understand why your Twitter (sorry, "X") feed is exploding, TLDR is your express lane to tech awareness. Boot up your day with us, and never miss a digital beat.

TLDR: We read the boring stuff so you don't have to. You're welcome.]]></description>
    <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Three minute daily tech news briefing covering Silicon Valley startups AI crypto and industry trends.]]></itunes:summary>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    <image>
      <url>https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png</url>
      <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
      <title>TLDR</title>
    </image>
    <itunes:category text="Technology &gt; Tech News, Business &gt; Tech Business, News &gt; Tech News"/>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:keywords>tech,digital,startups,AI,crypto</itunes:keywords>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&apos;s $14B Scale AI Gambit: Young Genius Takes the Helm</title>
      <itunes:title>Meta&apos;s $14B Scale AI Gambit: Young Genius Takes the Helm</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into Meta's strategic $14.3 billion investment in Scale AI, marking a pivotal moment in the tech industry's AI race. The episode unpacks the significance of Meta acquiring a 49% stake in Scale AI and their groundbreaking move to bring onboard Alexandr Wang, the 28-year-old billionaire prodigy, to spearhead their superintelligence initiatives. Beyond Meta's power play, we explore the potential disruption in the payment landscape as retail giants Walmart and Amazon contemplate launching their own stablecoins. The episode also covers Shopify's game-changing partnership with Coinbase and Stripe, introducing USDC stablecoin payments globally through Coinbase's Base network. We examine the fascinating intersection of military and tech sectors with the Army Reserve's new "Detachment 201" initiative, bringing together minds from Palantir, Meta, and OpenAI. The episode concludes with a cautionary tale about Meta's AI app privacy breach, highlighting the delicate balance between innovation and user privacy in today's rapidly evolving tech landscape.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/0316273805)
• "Scale: The Universal Laws of Growth, Innovation, Sustainability - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/014311090X)
• "The Future of Money: How the Digital Revolution Is Transforming Currencies - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/1647820189)
• "Inside the Military's New Innovation Corps" (https://www.wired.com/military-innovation)
• "The Rise of Stablecoins" (https://www.coindesk.com/learn/what-are-stablecoins)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[OpenAI expands cloud partnerships with Google Cloud and CoreWeave, marking shift in tech alliances and computing infrastructure]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into Meta's strategic $14.3 billion investment in Scale AI, marking a pivotal moment in the tech industry's AI race. The episode unpacks the significance of Meta acquiring a 49% stake in Scale AI and their groundbreaking move to bring onboard Alexandr Wang, the 28-year-old billionaire prodigy, to spearhead their superintelligence initiatives. Beyond Meta's power play, we explore the potential disruption in the payment landscape as retail giants Walmart and Amazon contemplate launching their own stablecoins. The episode also covers Shopify's game-changing partnership with Coinbase and Stripe, introducing USDC stablecoin payments globally through Coinbase's Base network. We examine the fascinating intersection of military and tech sectors with the Army Reserve's new "Detachment 201" initiative, bringing together minds from Palantir, Meta, and OpenAI. The episode concludes with a cautionary tale about Meta's AI app privacy breach, highlighting the delicate balance between innovation and user privacy in today's rapidly evolving tech landscape.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/0316273805)
• "Scale: The Universal Laws of Growth, Innovation, Sustainability - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/014311090X)
• "The Future of Money: How the Digital Revolution Is Transforming Currencies - Book" (https://amazon.com/dp/1647820189)
• "Inside the Military's New Innovation Corps" (https://www.wired.com/military-innovation)
• "The Rise of Stablecoins" (https://www.coindesk.com/learn/what-are-stablecoins)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749966040/airtable_audio/recTCx6OizA7xcN4g-9a0f.mp3" 
                 length="904615"
                 type="audio/mpeg"
                 bitrate="128000"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recTCx6OizA7xcN4g</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:01:53</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>tech,updates,news</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&apos;s $110B Dilemma: Bitcoin vs Buybacks</title>
      <itunes:title>Apple&apos;s $110B Dilemma: Bitcoin vs Buybacks</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into MicroStrategy CEO Michael Saylor's bold proposition to Apple regarding their $110 billion cash reserves. As Apple grapples with a 17% stock decline despite implementing a massive buyback program, Saylor suggests a revolutionary alternative: investing in Bitcoin, which has shown impressive growth during the same period. The episode explores this intriguing intersection of traditional tech giants and cryptocurrency, highlighting GameStop's recent $513 million Bitcoin acquisition. We also examine Ripple Labs' strategic $5 million investment in blockchain education across the Asia-Pacific region, demonstrating the growing emphasis on cryptocurrency infrastructure and education. The narrative extends to Franklin Templeton's innovative tokenized asset developments and CityFibre's groundbreaking UK broadband initiatives. The episode concludes with Amazon's landmark $20 billion investment in Pennsylvania's data center infrastructure, marking the state's largest private sector investment and promising significant job creation in the AI and cloud computing sectors.

Further Reading:
• "The Bitcoin Standard" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/1119473861)
• "Digital Gold: Bitcoin and the Inside Story of the Misfits and Millionaires Trying to Reinvent Money" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/006236250X)
• "The Future of Money: How the Digital Revolution Is Transforming Currencies and Finance" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/0674270282)
• "Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System" (https://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf)
• "Understanding Corporate Bitcoin Investment" (https://www.microstrategy.com/en/bitcoin)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Tech news: Chinese chip smuggling, Taiwan export controls, AI healthcare gaps, Apple's LRM debate, Waymo protests, influencer market growth]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into MicroStrategy CEO Michael Saylor's bold proposition to Apple regarding their $110 billion cash reserves. As Apple grapples with a 17% stock decline despite implementing a massive buyback program, Saylor suggests a revolutionary alternative: investing in Bitcoin, which has shown impressive growth during the same period. The episode explores this intriguing intersection of traditional tech giants and cryptocurrency, highlighting GameStop's recent $513 million Bitcoin acquisition. We also examine Ripple Labs' strategic $5 million investment in blockchain education across the Asia-Pacific region, demonstrating the growing emphasis on cryptocurrency infrastructure and education. The narrative extends to Franklin Templeton's innovative tokenized asset developments and CityFibre's groundbreaking UK broadband initiatives. The episode concludes with Amazon's landmark $20 billion investment in Pennsylvania's data center infrastructure, marking the state's largest private sector investment and promising significant job creation in the AI and cloud computing sectors.

Further Reading:
• "The Bitcoin Standard" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/1119473861)
• "Digital Gold: Bitcoin and the Inside Story of the Misfits and Millionaires Trying to Reinvent Money" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/006236250X)
• "The Future of Money: How the Digital Revolution Is Transforming Currencies and Finance" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/0674270282)
• "Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System" (https://bitcoin.org/bitcoin.pdf)
• "Understanding Corporate Bitcoin Investment" (https://www.microstrategy.com/en/bitcoin)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749966043/airtable_audio/reccUlJXAOQLstN0W-a616.mp3" 
                 length="1214769"
                 type="audio/mpeg"
                 bitrate="128000"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">reccUlJXAOQLstN0W</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:02:32</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>tech,updates,news</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York&apos;s AI Safety Law: A Digital Wake-Up Call</title>
      <itunes:title>New York&apos;s AI Safety Law: A Digital Wake-Up Call</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into New York's groundbreaking AI Safety legislation, marking a pivotal moment in AI regulation. The RAISE Act emerges as America's potential first legally mandated transparency framework for frontier AI models, requiring industry giants like OpenAI, Google, and Anthropic to provide detailed safety documentation for their most sophisticated AI systems. The episode explores parallel developments across the global tech landscape, including Chinese AI companies' innovative responses to U.S. chip restrictions and Amazon's ambitious $13 billion investment plan in Australian digital infrastructure. We examine critical insights from an Oxford University study highlighting the disconnect between AI's theoretical capabilities and practical healthcare applications. The discussion concludes with Google's experimental Audio Overviews feature, offering listeners a comprehensive snapshot of how today's technological developments are actively shaping our digital future. This essential overview connects the dots between AI regulation, international tech competition, healthcare innovation, and digital infrastructure development, providing crucial context for understanding the rapidly evolving technology landscape.

Further Reading:
• 'The Age of AI: And Our Human Future - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B093G9TS91)
• 'Atlas of AI: Power, Politics, and the Planetary Costs of Artificial Intelligence - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B08WK3TNVH)
• 'The Coming Wave: Technology, Power, and the Twenty-first Century's Greatest Dilemma - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B0BVDQ11CY)
• 'AI Regulation Global Overview' (https://www.brookings.edu/articles/ai-regulation-global-overview)
• 'The AI Revolution: Balancing Innovation and Safety' (https://www.technologyreview.com/ai-safety-innovation)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Chinese engineers bypass US chip controls, Waymo faces protests, Apple research reveals AI limitations, Chess.com rises, AI enters emergency services]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[In this eye-opening episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into New York's groundbreaking AI Safety legislation, marking a pivotal moment in AI regulation. The RAISE Act emerges as America's potential first legally mandated transparency framework for frontier AI models, requiring industry giants like OpenAI, Google, and Anthropic to provide detailed safety documentation for their most sophisticated AI systems. The episode explores parallel developments across the global tech landscape, including Chinese AI companies' innovative responses to U.S. chip restrictions and Amazon's ambitious $13 billion investment plan in Australian digital infrastructure. We examine critical insights from an Oxford University study highlighting the disconnect between AI's theoretical capabilities and practical healthcare applications. The discussion concludes with Google's experimental Audio Overviews feature, offering listeners a comprehensive snapshot of how today's technological developments are actively shaping our digital future. This essential overview connects the dots between AI regulation, international tech competition, healthcare innovation, and digital infrastructure development, providing crucial context for understanding the rapidly evolving technology landscape.

Further Reading:
• 'The Age of AI: And Our Human Future - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B093G9TS91)
• 'Atlas of AI: Power, Politics, and the Planetary Costs of Artificial Intelligence - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B08WK3TNVH)
• 'The Coming Wave: Technology, Power, and the Twenty-first Century's Greatest Dilemma - Book' (https://amazon.com/dp/B0BVDQ11CY)
• 'AI Regulation Global Overview' (https://www.brookings.edu/articles/ai-regulation-global-overview)
• 'The AI Revolution: Balancing Innovation and Safety' (https://www.technologyreview.com/ai-safety-innovation)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749966097/airtable_audio/receBwoCDKgONuVxS-177d8.mp3" 
                 length="846154"
                 type="audio/mpeg"
                 bitrate="128000"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">receBwoCDKgONuVxS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:01:46</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>tech,updates,news</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Revolution: TikTok Creates, Amazon Streams, China&apos;s Brain Tech Leaps</title>
      <itunes:title>AI Revolution: TikTok Creates, Amazon Streams, China&apos;s Brain Tech Leaps</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[In this groundbreaking episode of TLDR, we dive into three transformative technological developments reshaping our digital landscape in June 2025. TikTok's revolutionary Symphony AI suite emerges as a game-changer for content creators, introducing sophisticated video generation tools that can transform text and images into engaging five-second video ads instantly. The landmark partnership between Amazon and Roku marks a pivotal moment in connected-TV advertising, creating unprecedented access to over 80% of US households and delivering impressive efficiency gains with 40% more unique viewers reached. Perhaps most remarkably, China's successful implementation of its first brain-computer interface represents a significant leap forward in neurotechnology, featuring neural electrodes one-fifth the size of Neuralink's technology. The breakthrough enables tetraplegic patients to control electronic devices through thought alone, marking China as only the second country to achieve this milestone in invasive BCI technology. This episode captures the rapid acceleration of AI integration across marketing, advertising, and medical technology, offering insights into how these innovations are fundamentally changing human capabilities and industry practices.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/B093G9TS91)
• "Brain-Computer Interfaces: An International Assessment of Research and Development Trends" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/3540748520)
• "The Future of Digital Advertising" (https://adweek.com/digital-advertising-future)
• "Understanding Brain-Computer Interface Technology" (https://nature.com/articles/bci-technology-review)
• "TikTok for Business: The Ultimate Guide" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/B08P5KXVQ2)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[OpenAI expands cloud partnerships with Google Cloud and CoreWeave, marking shift in tech alliances and computing infrastructure]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[In this groundbreaking episode of TLDR, we dive into three transformative technological developments reshaping our digital landscape in June 2025. TikTok's revolutionary Symphony AI suite emerges as a game-changer for content creators, introducing sophisticated video generation tools that can transform text and images into engaging five-second video ads instantly. The landmark partnership between Amazon and Roku marks a pivotal moment in connected-TV advertising, creating unprecedented access to over 80% of US households and delivering impressive efficiency gains with 40% more unique viewers reached. Perhaps most remarkably, China's successful implementation of its first brain-computer interface represents a significant leap forward in neurotechnology, featuring neural electrodes one-fifth the size of Neuralink's technology. The breakthrough enables tetraplegic patients to control electronic devices through thought alone, marking China as only the second country to achieve this milestone in invasive BCI technology. This episode captures the rapid acceleration of AI integration across marketing, advertising, and medical technology, offering insights into how these innovations are fundamentally changing human capabilities and industry practices.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/B093G9TS91)
• "Brain-Computer Interfaces: An International Assessment of Research and Development Trends" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/3540748520)
• "The Future of Digital Advertising" (https://adweek.com/digital-advertising-future)
• "Understanding Brain-Computer Interface Technology" (https://nature.com/articles/bci-technology-review)
• "TikTok for Business: The Ultimate Guide" - Book (https://amazon.com/dp/B08P5KXVQ2)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1749966460/airtable_audio/recn9E2Ptdlu7k0fe-7025c.mp3" 
                 length="1699077"
                 type="audio/mpeg"
                 bitrate="128000"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recn9E2Ptdlu7k0fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:03:32</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>tech,updates,news</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&apos;s AI Stumble: Wall Street&apos;s Cold Shoulder at WWDC</title>
      <itunes:title>Apple&apos;s AI Stumble: Wall Street&apos;s Cold Shoulder at WWDC</itunes:title>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
      <description><![CDATA[In this revealing episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into the ripple effects of Apple's underwhelming AI announcements at WWDC 2025. The tech giant's stock dropped 1.5% following their presentation, where the much-hyped AI features failed to meet market expectations. The episode unpacks Apple's focus on their "Liquid Glass" interface redesign and notably absent AI capabilities, including the delayed intelligent Siri updates. Beyond Apple, we explore the UK government's controversial deployment of the "Humphrey" AI toolkit, built on technology from OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google, raising questions about regulatory independence. The narrative extends to Taiwan's significant move to restrict semiconductor technology exports to China, aligning with US policies and highlighting TSMC's crucial role in the global tech supply chain. This interconnected analysis reveals how AI development, government oversight, and semiconductor politics are reshaping the technology landscape, making this episode essential listening for anyone following the intersection of tech innovation and global politics.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Age-AI-Our-Human-Future/dp/0316273805)
• "Chip War: The Fight for the World's Most Critical Technology" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Chip-War-Worlds-Critical-Technology/dp/1982172002)
• "The Coming Wave: Technology, Power, and the Twenty-first Century's Greatest Dilemma" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Coming-Wave-Technology-Twenty-first-Greatest/dp/0593299183)
• "AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/AI-Superpowers-China-Silicon-Valley/dp/132854639X)]]></description>
      <itunes:summary><![CDATA[]]></itunes:summary>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[In this revealing episode of TLDR - Tech Lowdown, Digital Rundown, we dive into the ripple effects of Apple's underwhelming AI announcements at WWDC 2025. The tech giant's stock dropped 1.5% following their presentation, where the much-hyped AI features failed to meet market expectations. The episode unpacks Apple's focus on their "Liquid Glass" interface redesign and notably absent AI capabilities, including the delayed intelligent Siri updates. Beyond Apple, we explore the UK government's controversial deployment of the "Humphrey" AI toolkit, built on technology from OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google, raising questions about regulatory independence. The narrative extends to Taiwan's significant move to restrict semiconductor technology exports to China, aligning with US policies and highlighting TSMC's crucial role in the global tech supply chain. This interconnected analysis reveals how AI development, government oversight, and semiconductor politics are reshaping the technology landscape, making this episode essential listening for anyone following the intersection of tech innovation and global politics.

Further Reading:
• "The Age of AI: And Our Human Future" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Age-AI-Our-Human-Future/dp/0316273805)
• "Chip War: The Fight for the World's Most Critical Technology" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Chip-War-Worlds-Critical-Technology/dp/1982172002)
• "The Coming Wave: Technology, Power, and the Twenty-first Century's Greatest Dilemma" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/Coming-Wave-Technology-Twenty-first-Greatest/dp/0593299183)
• "AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order" - Book (https://www.amazon.com/AI-Superpowers-China-Silicon-Valley/dp/132854639X)]]></content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/video/upload/v1750007987/airtable_audio/recvymWDmPcA7I8qz-f0aa6.mp3" 
                 length="1950769"
                 type="audio/mpeg"
                 bitrate="128000"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">recvymWDmPcA7I8qz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:04:04</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:keywords>tech,updates,news</itunes:keywords>
      <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>