<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>TLDR</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>WonderAI</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Daily three minute tech news briefing covering AI startups crypto and Silicon Valley developments.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Stay ahead of the tech curve in just three minutes a day with TLDR, your essential morning briefing on all things digital. From groundbreaking AI developments to cryptocurrency rollercoasters, Silicon Valley power plays to game-changing startup moves, TLDR distills the tech world's most important stories into clear, concise updates that matter.

Every weekday, TLDR cuts through the noise to deliver a perfectly calibrated mix of must-know news and fascinating developments, minus the technical jargon and endless analysis. Whether you're a tech industry insider or simply want to understand why your social media feed is buzzing, this podcast transforms complex tech narratives into accessible, engaging stories that keep you informed and make you sound like the smartest person in any conversation.

Disclaimer: This podcast provides news and information for general educational purposes only. The content should not be considered as financial, legal, or professional advice. Views expressed are those of the hosts and guests, and do not necessarily reflect official positions of any referenced companies or organizations.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>WonderAI</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1749955134/airtable_audio/recKPYPQwyJ7deMOy-20c32.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Technology > Tech News, Business > Tech Business, News > Tech News" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/tldr.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>