<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wack Pack Stories</title>
    <link>https://airtable.com/app8RF1bwHUrradMB/pagdckUa8gmwDiUrv/form</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>Optimus Prime </itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Explores memorable characters and outrageous moments from Howard Stern Show Wack Pack history through archived recordings.</itunes:summary>
    <description>Journey into the wild and wonderful world of the Howard Stern Show's most colorful characters through Wack Pack Stories. This captivating series delves deep into the unforgettable moments, legendary personalities, and outrageous encounters that have made the Wack Pack a cultural phenomenon. Each episode uncovers the fascinating stories behind these unique individuals who have become an integral part of radio history.

From their first appearances to their most memorable interactions, Wack Pack Stories chronicles the authentic, unfiltered, and often hilarious experiences that have entertained millions of listeners. Through carefully curated archives and insider perspectives, this podcast preserves and celebrates the legacy of these distinctive personalities who have helped shape the landscape of entertainment radio.

Disclaimer: This podcast contains adult content and language. All content related to the Howard Stern Show and its personalities is presented for entertainment purposes. This description is experimental and was generated by artificial intelligence.</description>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Optimus Prime </itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>pukka.flashy5g@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://res.cloudinary.com/dumslp4el/image/upload/v1750007787/airtable_audio/recDpa1nfK149mwlL-c02e6.jpg" />
    <itunes:category text="Comedy > Comedy Interviews, Entertainment > TV & Film, Society & Culture > Personal Journals" />
    <copyright>(c) 2025. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://neelketkar.github.io/optimus-prime/feeds/wack-pack-stories.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Airtable</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>